( Man 's voice echoes ) ' One , one , one ... Two , two , two ... three , three ... '
( Gospel chant ) II know it was some blood
[ music ] Oh , I know it was some blood
[ music ] Yeah , I know it was a blood for me
[ music ] It tell you that one clay when I was lost
[ music ] You know that he died upon the cross [ music ]
( [ music ] Song over audio )
( Indistinct chanting )
( Man ) Jesus ! Jesus !
( Man ) [ music ] Jesus knows ! Oh , yeah . Hallelujah !
Yeah , yeah ... It 's all right .
It 's all right .
I tell you something , you know ...
- Jesus is here today . - ( All ) Yeah !
If you don 't feel it , you ain 't got no business being here !
- Am I right ? Right on ? - ( Woman ) Amen !
( Luther ) ' It 's like this : you see , I 've been a Minister for a long time .
'I like it .
'And I 've been at this church for ... I mean , this church is very good .
'In fact , the people are very warm to me and they love me .
'They love me very much , which is very good .
'Because that pulls something out of me , it 's what is giving them something .
I wanna get a little higher note . I wanna go up there !
'My official title is Reverend Luther Williams .
'I also work as a chauffeur and a stableman
'part-time to help support my family .
'I work for Dr Hess Green .
'And he 's an addict .
'He 's not a criminal . He 's a victim . '
( Sirens wailing )
'He 's addicted to blood .
( Hess ) Why don 't you park it over there ?
( Footsteps approaching )
- Dr Green , I 'm Jack Sargent . - Good to meet you , Mr Sargent .
Come this way .
( Hess ) ' And Jesus said unto them ,
" ' Who so eateth my flesh and drinketh my blood ,
" ' hath eternal life .
" ' And I will raise him up at the last clay .
" ' For my flesh is meat indeed ,
" ' and my blood is drink indeed .
" ' He that eateth my flesh and drinketh my blood
" ' dwelleth in me and I in them " '
( Sargent ) ' Dr Green , I want you to meet your new assistant , Mr George Meda . '
( Meda ) ' Dr Green , I know these things are better left unsaid ,
'but , er ... I just want you to know that I 'm very proud to be employed by you . '
It 's not a city I know well , but I 've always loved that music .
Well , it 's pretty silly , but as long as you 're out here on the outskirts ,
the museum is just fantastic .
Some of these terracotta pieces , they 're really nice .
( Indistinct dialogue )
( Engine starts )
This is us .
[ music ] By the Christians it is written that in the Black Myrthian Age
[ music ] There existed an addiction to blood among its people
[ music ] Thousands of slaves are bled to death
[ music ] But murdered in such a way the slaves could not die
[ music ] There was visited upon them a curse that they should live forever
[ music ] Unless the shadow of a cross , an implement of torture
[ music ] Touched their darkened heart
[ music ] But oh ! But oh ! But oh !
[ music ] Since Christ ... Since Christ had not come yet
[ music ] And the cross did not exist
[ music ] Don 't you know , don 't you know
[ music ] Don 't you know they were called to walk the earth
[ music ] Till the Christians came ?
[ music ] Oh , my , my , my ... '
[ music ] My , my , my ...
[ music ] The blood of the thing is the truth of the thing
[ music ] Oh , the blood of the thing is the truth of the thing
[ music ] They had come to be addicted to truth
[ music ] Till the Christians came I
Would you take Mr Meda 's things to the south bedroom , please ?
Very good , sir .
How do you do , sir ?
Which would you prefer by the way , Meda or George ?
I thought I heard Mr Woods call you Meda .
- ( Meda ) I hate George . - It 's Meda , then . See you inside .
Luther , what 's wrong with this ? It seems to be discoloring .
( Luther ) Most likely it 's the heat .
I really have to tell you this story about this very good friend of mine .
Thank you . That was a very delicious meal , I liked it very much .
Thank you very much .
What was I saying ? Oh , I was gonna tell you this story ...
This friend of mine 's a director , you know , and we were in ...
Oh , my god !
( Chuckles )
Fantastic ! That 's so fantastic .
I really appreciate this so much . It 's really ...
That is my first good meal in clays , you know ?
- I 've been ... out a lot . - I 'm glad you enjoyed it , Mr Meda .
Anyway , I was saying about this friend who was directing a picture in Holland ,
and the thing you 've got to know about this story
is that in Dutch , " Cut " means " cunt " .
Thank you very much . Very sweet of you .
He was directing this scene and there was a lot of people on the street ...
Suddenly he yells , " Cunt ... Cut ! "
And all these people get very upset at him ,
and they start throwing things at him because he did a dirty word .
Anyway , the guy who 's supposed to be the interpreter is in the hotel room ,
he was racked out because he was at a party the night before .
I know cos I was there , and it was really fantastic .
( Footsteps )
Anyway ... Oh , my god . I don 't believe it .
This is really terrific .
You don 't know how much I appreciate this .
It 's been a long time since I had a good meal .
Er ... anyway ... the interpreter comes downstairs , right ?
And he tells them that you can 't say " cut " in Holland ,
because you 'll get into a lot of trouble .
So we go back to the end of the scene , and the guy yells , " Cunt ! "
Dig it ? You understand what I mean ?
It 's a very fantastic thing , I thought that was terrific .
I mean , it 's a fantastic thing , what he did .
( Hess ) Yes .
Anyway , I don 't know , if I ...
If I really believed in a desire
I don 't think it would frighten me so much , do you understand that ?
I think I know what you 're saying .
The idea of desire is very much a part of our culture .
After all , the Myrthians thought they had a desire for blood , not a need for it .
But it was a need .
( Chuckles ) Good grief .
( High-pitched ringing )
I think what we 're talking about ... is hunger .
Do you know what hunger is ? I don 't know what hunger is .
I sit and I eat , but I don 't know what hunger is .
( [ music ] African chanting )
( Echoing footsteps )
Dr Green ... I 'm Jack Sargent . Good to see you . Come this way ...
I 'm Jack Sargent . Good to see you .
( Chanting intensifies )
( Chanting slows down and echoes )
( Chanting quickens and intensifies )
( ' Resonating screams ' )
( [ music ] Classical music playing )
Meda ?
Medal
( Meda ) I 'm drunk , OK ?
Not drunk enough to jump out of that tree .
Ah , look , will you do me a favor ? Don 't try to impress me , all right ?
- All right . - ( Meda ) OK .
Is there anything I can do ?
Yes , there is something you can do . Don 't bullshit me .
All right .
Would you do me a favor and hand me my drink down there ?
- Where is it ? - No , over there , right at your feet .
Right down there , OK ?
There .
Thank you .
( Hess coughs and grunts )
( Meda ) What are you doing ? What are you ... ?
You put something in my drink .
You put something in my goddamn drink , I saw you !
What 's in the drink ?
I removed a few dead ants . That all right ?
( Meda ) I 'm neurotic , OK ?
( Hess ) What does that mean , " I 'm neurotic " ?
( Meda ) Ah , actually it means that this hasn 't got anything to do with you .
OK ? May I have it ? I need it .
- It has nothing to do with me ? - No .
Except it is my tree and my rope .
You see , that would give the authorities the right to invade my privacy
with all sorts of embarrassing questions .
Ah , Dr Green , actually I thought I 'd throw myself in one of your lakes .
But I have an absolute horror of drowning .
Then your horrors outweigh your manners .
I tried not to involve you .
( Hess snorts )
Mr Meda ... there 's no possible way for you to know this ,
but I 'm the only colored on the block .
( Meda giggles )
And if another black man washes ashore around here ,
you can believe the authorities would drag me out for questioning .
Will you please come out of that tree ?
I got into this very heavy idea about suicide .
And I tried it once before , this was a long time ago .
I was actually sitting on the floor of the kitchen where I was living .
This was in New York .
And , er ... I really had this idea ...
It was a very schizophrenic idea , because I was , you know
that
I was a victim on one hand ,
and on the other hand , I was , er ... a murderer .
You understand ? It was very complicated , but that 's what I was going through .
And it was like the murderer ...
I can 't start with the murderer , I got to start with the victim .
The victim didn 't want to die .
I didn 't know why , everything was OK but I didn 't want to die .
And then the murderer , you know , that 's what ...
And I was in the kitchen and I took a knife and put it right to my neck .
I couldn 't do anything .
I just couldn 't do it .
It was like ... What am I saying ?
It was like ... the murderer let the victim cut .
It was like a cat-and-mouse game . You understand that ?
You know that feeling ?
" To the black male children ...
" Philosophy is a prison .
" It disregards the uncustomary things about you .
" The result of individual thought is applicable only to itself .
" There is a dreadful need in Man to teach .
" It destroys the pure instinct to learn .
" The navigator learns from the stars .
" The stars teach nothing .
" The sun opens the mind and sheds light on the flowers .
" The eyes shame the pages of any book .
" Gesture destroys concept .
" Involvement mortifies vanity .
" You are the despised of the earth .
" That is as if you were water in the desert .
" To be adored on this planet is to be a symbol of success .
" And you must not succeed on any terms ,
" because life is endless .
" You are as nameless as a flower .
" You are the child of Venus ,
" and her natural affection is lust .
" She will touch your belly with her tongue
" but you must not suffer in it ,
" for love is all there is
" and you are cannon fodder in its defense . "
( [ music ] Faint Jazz music plays )
( [ music ] Jazz music on radio )
( Gunshot )
( Door opens )
( Labored breathing )
And O Lord
that as we are baptized into the death of thy blessed son ,
our savior , Jesus Christ ,
and by continually mortifying our corrupt affections ,
we may be buried with him .
Through ... the grave and gate of death ,
we may pass to our joyful resurrection .
By his merit
who died the same ...
( Screams )
( Echoes )
( Explosion )
( Doctor ) Good god !
A muse lingers in the room
and dangles a melody in the air like a ripe fig .
And we eat our summer soup around the great table ,
humming into our plates some court phrase
then dropping it for a second ,
till a bird in the window sings it clearly
and darts towards the river .
- There 's your father . - Dad !
Enrico ! What a surprise , no one told me you were coming .
- How are you , son ? - Fine .
- How 's school going ? - Fine . Never been better .
- Yes ? And French ? - Ca Va bien .
Ca Va bien ? Formidable ...
( Speak French together )
- Did you get something to drink ? - Nope .
- What would you like ? - Oh , anything .
- Some ginger ale ? - Yeah .
- ( Hess ) Archie ? - Yes ?
- Can we get a ginger ale ? - But of course , sir .
( Indistinct dialogue )
( People converse in French )
( Chanting intensifies )
( Chanting over dialogue )
( Woman ) ' All right , I 'll do it . ' ( Man ) ' When , baby ? '
Today .
Today when ? I mean , like in this hour ... ?
I promise you we 'll make a big take today .
Yeah , a big one . I can feel it .
This is the love movement , man ! Where you comin ' from ?
Be cool , bro . Cool it .
( Conversation stops abruptly )
( Indistinct dialogue starts )
- I 'm gonna help you . - When , baby ?
Today .
When today , is what I wanna know . See , my time is money .
Soon ! I mean ...
( Man ) Be cool , be cool , be cool ... Hey , look at y 'all .
- Nothin ' here but a slick brother ... - How d 'you know , man ?
( Indistinct dialogue )
( Woman ) This sort of thing ...
If we 're going to the Derby , we need some cash .
All right !
There ...
Well , I 'll take care of that soon .
That 's what you been sayin for the past hour .
Well , ain 't nobody been in here . I mean ...
Come on , move it .
Do you know a girl named Dolores Kincaid ?
No .
Dolores Kincaid ?
Well , you know , you look just like the boyfriend she had
before she moved to Seattle .
I do ?
Yes . I saw him with her once at the Apollo .
- And you look just like him . - ( Hess ) I see .
There 's this strung-out child lives downstairs from her , you know ?
And she was just screaming and yelling ,
and I didn 't know what in the world to do .
So I said , " Well , I have to put a stop to this . "
So I decided to call the police .
So I called them and they came and got her , you know , and ...
Sit down , girl .
( Woman ) Hmm ?
I said sit down .
Oh , I know what I 'm gonna do ...
Hmm ...
Hmm , yeah .
( [ music ] African chanting )
Help ! Kill him !
( Screams )
( Echoing laughter )
( Retching )
( Phone rings )
( Hess ) ' Hello ? ' ( Ganja ) Hello , is my husband there ?
I haven 't the slightest idea who your husband is , madam .
George Meda is my husband , and I wanna speak to him . Put him on the phone !
'Do you hear me talking to you ? '
He 's not here now .
( Aircraft engine noise )
( Phone rings )
( Hess sighs heavily )
Hello ?
I called the museum and they told me George was there .
'Now you put him on the phone . I don 't want no more of his shit ! '
Look , Mrs Meda , I have had a very difficult morning and if ...
( Ganja ) I have had a very difficult fucking six months !
- It 's not possible to talk to Mr Meda now . - What do you mean , it 's not possible ?
- ( Hess ) He has disappeared . - ' Disappeared ? '
'George freaked out on you ?
'He ain 't disappeared . He 'll show up .
'He 's going crazy again , that 's what 's happened . He 'll be back .
'All right , man , I 'll put it to you straight . '
I just got in from Amsterdam and I do not have enough money for a decent hotel .
Now since he already has a room there ,
if I could come to your place and stay there
for just a few clays and wait for him ...
Where are you , Mrs Meda ?
I 'm at the goddamn airport , that 's where I am !
Tell me where you are exactly and I will send a limousine for you .
I 'm standing in front of Pan American and the driver can 't miss me ,
cos I 'm that evil !
Tell your boss I 'm here .
I am Dr Green .
( Both laugh )
Could you tell me where I could change ?
I haven 't changed since I left Amsterdam . I 'm very tired .
( [ music ] Soft jazz playing )
I have a friend who 's a ballet dancer .
And he went to Mexico to dance at the Palace of Fine Arts .
That 's where he scored this stuff , from Mexico .
And , er ...
I think he came up with a really fantastic , ingenious thing to do .
He puts the grass in a prophylactic ,
and rolls it up so that it 's like a suppository , you know ?
And then he just ... you know ?
And then he puts on all these shorts , right ?
Like four pairs , he pulls them on .
Cos they 've got these clogs at Customs , you know when you go through ?
And they can smell anything .
Well , almost anything !
And ... hey , man ,
I think it takes a very heavy cat to come up with that , I really do .
Don 't you think so ?
Come ...
( [ music ] African chanting )
( Thunderclap )
( [ music ] Chanting intensifies )
Hess ? Hess !
Hess !
Hess ?
( Ladders rattling )
( Footsteps )
( Ganja gasps )
( Dogs barking in distance )
Thank you .
Why do you live in a house this size alone ?
That 's an impolite question .
A-ha ... they 're the only ones worth asking .
- ( Hess ) What do you want now ? - This instant ? Or now ?
Now .
Money .
Is there anything else ?
May I get you fresh coffee ?
No , thank you .
I would like some , Archie .
Do you sometimes feel overworked , Archie ?
Good heavens , no , madam . No , never .
( Hess ) Another impolite question .
I told you , I specialize in impolite questions ...
( Hess ) " They 're the only ones worth asking . "
They are !
When people answer them I know more about them then than I did before .
- What do they know about you ? - Nothing .
They know that you ask impolite questions .
Yes .
What is there to know about Ganja ?
( Crows cawing )
( Ganja ) Archie , when you get the grape jelly ...
And you are gonna get the grape jelly , right ?
Of course , madam .
Well , then , why don 't you get the grits
at the same time ?
( Archie ) The grits ?
Grits . Harmony grits . You know what harmony grits are , don 't you ?
- Harmony grits ? - Harmony grits .
Now , the other thing I wanted to ask you about is ,
I need an extension cord .
I have a record player that I wanna play downstairs .
( Archie ) For a record player ?
For a record player . You understand " a record player " ?
And you understand " extension cord " ?
So we got three things going :
we got some grape jelly , some harmony grits and an extension cord .
- Don 't we ? - Yes , madam .
- Thank you so much . - But of course , madam .
( Ganja ) Archie , how long you been here ?
Madam , I came with the house .
- You came with the house ? - Yes , ma 'am .
( Ganja ) You mean the plumbers came in and put you in ?
- ( Archie ) Precisely where ... ? - Right there !
- ( Archie ) Good heavens ! - You blew your peach .
( Giggles )
- Archie ! - That was rather humorous , madam .
( Raucous laughter )
Is red one of your favorite colors ?
I wore white cos I wore black when I got here , and I thought you 'd like this .
But if you like red , I 'll wear red .
I like red .
( Hess ) Look .
( Ganja ) Looks like blood !
( Distant laughter )
( Hess ) I haven 't the slightest idea .
Yeah , I remember . It really doesn 't matter , anyway .
- ( Hess ) It 's a good-looking saddle , Luther . - Glad you like it .
It 's good leather and it 's comfortable .
Good morning .
I 'll see you around .
( Ganja ) What would you like to have for dinner ?
Cook whatever you do best .
Give me a suggestion .
Doesn 't matter as long as it doesn 't have a lot of grease in it .
( Ganja laughs )
- Hess ? - Yes ?
Did I hear you say you didn 't believe in marriage ?
( scoffs )
No , I never said any such thing .
( Engine starts )
( Horn blows )
( Traffic noise over dialogue )
Archie , you forgot the wine .
Oh , madam ! Dr Green keeps a very good wine cellar .
Oh , good . Where is it ?
I think we should wait for the doctor to return .
He doesn 't allow anyone in the cellar .
The only time I go ... is with him .
Archie , I need the wine .
OK , I 'll tell you what we 'll do .
You tell me where the wine cellar is and I 'll go and get the wine ,
and I won 't tell Dr Green that you told me .
- But Mrs Meda ... - Archie !
I said I need the wine .
Do I make myself clear ?
Very well ... madam .
Thank you .
My pleasure .
( Screaming )
( Baby cooing )
( TV program playing )
( Baby starts crying )
( Door closes )
Hey , I 'm sorry .
You did make a special effort for dinner tonight , didn 't you ?
Archie cooked .
I couldn 't get it together .
Are you all right ?
I just couldn 't fix dinner .
The soup 's very good .
I know you killed my husband ...
I beg your pardon .
... because you have his body in the freezer in the basement .
( Approaching footsteps )
Will you clear the plates , Archie ? We don 't seem to be very hungry .
( Glass shattering )
( Ganja ) When I was about 10 or 12 years old ,
my favorite time of the year was winter because of the snow .
And I made the best snowballs in all of Boston .
I was in the best snowball fights , and I always won .
This particular clay ,
it was just snowballs flying , it was all you could see ,
that was all you could feel .
Some hit hard , some hit soft and fell down behind your collar .
You could feel it in your muffler .
And I got home ... about 6 : 30 or 7 : 00 ,
cos I 'd been fighting since 3 : 00 in the afternoon .
And my mother said , " Where have you been ? "
I said , " I 've been having this tremendous snowball fight , it 's really fun .
" And I beat everybody , and everybody beat me . It was a tremendous day . "
And she slapped my face and said , " Where have you been ?
" Someone said they saw you being chased by a boy . "
I said , " We were all chasing each other ,
" because we were having a snowball fight . "
And she said , " You are a liar ... and a slut . "
And I said , " I swear to you that I was having a snowball fight . "
And she didn 't believe me .
She never believed me .
It was as though I was a disease .
I have a brother that 's ten years older than I am and a sister that 's eight years
older than I am .
So that I was obviously an accident .
And it was , " Ganja , I came down with Ganja , " you know ?
And I think that day , I decided
that I was a disease .
And I was gonna give her a full case of it .
That whatever it was that I was , she was gonna have it .
Maybe because she hurt me so badly .
All that time up till then , I really worked
for her to say , " I love you .
" You 're a wonderful girl , Ganja . "
She could never , ever say that .
The only thing she could ever bring herself to say was that I was beautiful .
And I loathed my beauty for that ..
... because she found it appealing .
But that was a very decisive clay in my life ,
because that day I decided
that I would provide for Ganja always .
Do whatever had to be clone .
Take whatever steps had to be taken .
But always take care of Ganja .
( Raucous laughter )
( Indistinct shouting and laughter )
( Both panting heavily )
Dearly beloved , we are assembled here in the presence of God
to join this man and this woman in holy marriage ,
which is instituted of God , regulated by his commandments ,
blessed by our lord savior , Jesus Christ ,
to be held in honor among all men ...
( [ music ] Background music over dialogue )
... in all love and honor , in all duty and service ,
in all faith and tenderness ,
to live with her and cherish her ,
according to the ordinance of God and the holy bond of marriage ?
- ' Please answer " I will " . ' - ( Hess ) ' I will . '
( Priest ) Ganja , will thou have this man to be thy husband
and will thou pledge thy troth to him in all love and honor ,
in all duty and service , in all faith and tenderness ,
to live with him and cherish him ,
according to the ordinance of God and the holy bond of marriage ?
- Please answer " I will " . - I will .
You still think I 'm psychotic ?
Of course .
Of course ?
Hm-mm .
And the fact that you think I 'm psychotic doesn 't frighten you ?
Oh , man ...
Everybody 's some kind of freak .
Everybody I know is into something .
You know ?
You 're into horror movies , I can dig it .
When it gets too heavy and I can 't cut it , believe me , you 'll be the first to know .
Meanwhile
let 's celebrate the divine art
and follow Nature .
Or let 's follow Nature and celebrate the divine art !
In all 69 positions , hmm ?
That 's called " taking care of business " .
Is that what it 's called ?
Why don 't you kiss me ?
You know I want you to live forever ?
( Laughs )
The way you 're acting , you 'd figure I was gonna live forever .
No , I mean I really want you to live forever .
( [ music ] African chanting )
( [ music ] Chanting intensifies )
( Ganja ) 'I had a strange dream last night .
'I dreamed you murdered me . '
( Hess ) ' The only perversions that can be comfortably condemned
'are the perversions of others .
'I will persist and survive without God 's or society 's sanction .
'I will not be tortured ,
'I will not be punished , I will not be guilty . '
( [ music ] Music over dialogue )
'The blood of our lord , Jesus Christ , which was shed for thee
'preserve thy body and soul for everlasting life . '
'Drink this in remembrance that Christ 's blood was shed for thee .
'And be thankful . '
( [ music ] Background music over audio )
( Electronic whirring )
( [ music ] African chanting intensifies )
Ganja ...
Here .
Take this , it 'll help you sleep .
I 'm sick .
I 'll be gone for a while . You 'll be all right until this evening .
We 're having a guest for dinner . I think you need a little distraction .
You 've got to understand that I won 't let anything happen to you .
How do you know Hess ?
He was a volunteer at my center .
- What kind of a center is it ? - A community recognition center .
( Ganja ) For people of all ages ?
( Richard ) For people of all ages . All over .
( Ganja ) ' What do you have ? I mean , any kind of dance classes ? '
( Richard ) We have dance classes , swimming , all kinds of ...
( [ music ] Music over audio )
( Screams )
( Dialogue inaudible )
( Frantic screaming )
( Ganja ) He 's alive ! ( Hess ) No !
- ( Ganja ) Hess , no ! He is alive ! - No !
- He 's alive ! - No !
( Ganja sobs )
( Screaming )
( Ganja ) Why am I always cold ?
I don 't know .
- Are you always cold ? - Hm-mm ...
What have you clone about it ?
Grown used to it .
What are you reading ?
It 's a guide to our destruction .
A solution .
Helgda , fourth queen of Myrthia .
" If you worship any god whatsoever ,
" and you believe this god to be good ,
" and if this god in which you trust be destroyed
" by forces dangerous to the survival of love ...
" ... and it is the implement by which this god was destroyed ...
" ... for this is the symbol of the destruction of life ,
" does cast a shadow on the heart ,
" then he shall be released into the bosom of his creator ,
" having suffered and tasted the blood of the womb of nature .
" He may sleep in her lap forever .
" Amen . "
If the shadow of the cross is against our heart ,
it 'll destroy us .
The cross is only an implement of torture .
Its shadow is the darkness it casts , you see ?
Nothing can survive in the shadows .
( [ music ] Gospel music )
( Applause and cheering )
Oh , we 've got to learn to let it go .
- Hallelujah ! - Yeah ...
Church ...
[ music ] Jesus
You know , I 'm high right now .
- But I 'm high on the Lord . - Thank you , Jesus !
Yeah ...
When you got a high on Jesus , you high !
Only one thing can bring you down , and that 's yourself , that 's the devil .
But the devil ain 't gonna come in here , I tell you .
I ain 't gonna let evil in here .
Evil is not coming between those doors back there .
( Whooping and cheering )
( Music and clapping starts )
- Say , " Thank you , Jesus . " - ( All ) Thank you , Jesus !
Raise your hands to God and say , " Thank you , Jesus . "
- ( All ) Thank you , Jesus ! - Say , " Thank you , Jesus . "
Say , " Thank you , Jesus . "
- Say , " Thank you , Jesus . " - ( All ) Thank you , Jesus "
Right now ...
If there 's anyone
who 'd like
to be prayed for ?
( Woman ) [ music ] My soul sings ...
If there 's anyone
that would like to be prayed for , will you come ?
We 're not playing in church , I mean business !
You might think I 'm playing , but I mean business .
- Cos I 'm from the same place you 're from . - ( Man ) Amen !
I 'm from the same place , I 'm no different from anybody else here .
That 's right . Ha-ha !
( [ music ] Piano starts )
( Indistinct singing )
( [ music ] Music over dialogue )
Today is the clay you give your life to Jesus .
Today is the clay that you give your life to Jesus .
[ music ] To Jesus !
[ music ] Oh , he knows
[ music ] All about
[ music ] Natural love ...
[ music ] Let me tell you that I need ...
( Indistinct lyrics )
( Luther ) He will guide us . God the father ...
In the name of Jesus !
In the name of Jesus ...
How do you feel , brother ?
How you feeling , brother ?
( Luther ) [ music ] Don 't you know that he died upon the cross ?
( [ music ] Singing intensifies )
( Labored breathing )
( [ music ] Gospel chanting )
Come with me .
Please , please , come with me .
( [ music ] African chanting )
( Echoing screams )
( Agonized screams continue )
( Screaming subsides )
( Sirens wailing )
( Sirens intensify )
( Sirens blaring )
( Medic ) ' What 's his name ? ' ( Ganja ) ' Dr Hess . '
- How old is he ? - Er ... 38 .
- You called the doctor when he took sick ? - Yes , I did .
- And he found out he 'd died ? - Yes , he did .
OK . Good . Thank you .
( Doors slam and engine starts )
( [ music ] Piano intro )
[ music ] There is a fountain filled with blood
[ music ] Drawn from Emmanuel 's veins
[ music ] And sinners ' plunged beneath the flood
[ music ] Lose all their guilty stains
[ music ] And sinners plunged beneath that flood
[ music ] Lose all their guilty stains ... [ music ]